Guide to the Joe Negri Collection, 1930-2014 CAM.JNC.2014
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Original Compositions, I.
  - Compositions with Bob McCully, 2.
    - "A Pittsburgher's Lament" (Box 4, Folder 242-247, Item 243)
      Holograph manuscript. Originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscriptions: Vocal - Lead Sheets - Yes We're Going Bananas 2nd set of Piano Parts Joe Negri Bob McCully Becks Show 1973 Rehearsal Schedule also inscribed
    - "True Love & the Maiden" (Box 4, Folder 242-247, Item 244)
    - "Pretty Girl"
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons Show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
      - "Pretty Girl" guitar (Box 6, Folder 361, Item 361)
      - "Pretty Girl" (Box 6, Folder 361, Item 361.1)
      - "Pretty Girl" bass (Box 6, Folder 361, Item 361.2)
      - "Pretty Girl" muted trumpet (Box 6, Folder 361, Item 361.3)
      - "Pretty Girl" drums (Box 6, Folder 361, Item 361.4)
    - "Guru" (Box 6, Folder 364-366)
      Holograph manuscript. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Beatle Mania" (Box 6, Folder 364-366, Item 364A)
      Holograph manuscript. 10 pages. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "The Bear Facts" (Box 6, Folder 364-366, Item 365)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten corrections. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "New Original Material" (Box 6, Folder 364-366, Item 366)
      Typed lists with handwritten notation. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "There's Nothing Left to Say", May 24, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 367-372, Item 367)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "There's Nothing Left to Say" (Box 6, Folder 367-372, Item 367.1)
      Typed lyrics. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Habit" (Box 6, Folder 367-372, Item 368)
      holography manuscript. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Love Is" (Box 6, Folder 367-372, Item 369)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. 2 pages. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "1st in Performance", May 31, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 367-372, Item 370)
    - "Woman in Stone" (Box 6, Folder 367-372, Item 371)
      Photostat of holograph manuscript. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Silent Movies" (Box 6, Folder 367-372, Item 372)
      Holograph manuscript. 2 pages. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Yvette" (Box 6, Folder 373-377, Item 373)
    - "Yvette" Final (Box 6, Folder 373-377, Item 374)
    - "Mame" (Box 6, Folder 373-377, Item 375)
      photocopy of typed lyrics with handwritten pencil notations. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "We Dialed the World but It Was Busy" (Box 6, Folder 373-377, Item 377)
      Photocopy of show order with penciled notations of people performing each scene/song. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Collegiate Medley" (Box 6, Folder 373-377, Item 378)
      mimeographed lyrics with penciled changes. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Spouses" (Box 6, Folder 379-384, Item 379)
      holograph manuscript. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "I.B.M. Girl" (Box 6, Folder 379-384, Item 380)
    - "Show Must Go On", May 30, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 379-384, Item 381)
    - "Give Love a Chance" (Box 6, Folder 379-384, Item 382)
    - "Intellectual Audience" (Box 6, Folder 379-384, Item 383)
      Photocopy of brief script with pencil notations. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Commercial Medley" (Box 6, Folder 379-384, Item 384)
      photocopy of typed lyrics with handwritten notations. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Roses" (Box 6, Folder 385-395, Item 385)
      Holograph manuscript and photocopy. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Wonderful Day - Medley" (Box 6, Folder 385-395, Item 386)
    - "Nice Work" (Box 6, Folder 385-395, Item 387)
    - "Closing" (Gallager & Sheen) (Box 6, Folder 385-395, Item 388)
    - "I Found My Love" (Box 6, Folder 385-395, Item 393)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Airline Stewardess" (Box 6, Folder 385-395, Item 394)
      Photostat of Holograph manuscript. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Victim of Love" (Box 6, Folder 385-395, Item 395)
    - "Snow White" (Box 6, Folder 396)
    - "Fair" (Box 6, Folder 397-402, Item 397)
    - "Knock Knock" (Box 6, Folder 397-402, Item 398)
    - "Poets of America, Arise" (Box 6, Folder 397-402, Item 400)
    - "The Triangle Song" (Box 6, Folder 397-402, Item 401)
      photostat of holograph manuscripts. Despite being in this category, the manuscripts note that the lyrics were by Si Bloom NOT Bob McCully. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "The Triangle Song" (Box 6, Folder 397-402, Item 402)
      Holograph manuscript. Despite being in this category, the manuscripts note that the lyrics were by Si Bloom NOT Bob McCully. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "If Stephen Foster Had Tried to Sell His Songs Today" (Box 6, Folder 403-406, Item 403)
      Photocopy of script. 4 pages. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Beautiful People" (Box 6, Folder 403-406, Item 404)
    - "Worlds in a Sunset" (Box 6, Folder 403-406, Item 405)
    - "Myron Cope" (Box 6, Folder 403-406, Item 406)
      photocopy of script. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Winston" (Box 6, Folder 407-416, Item 410)
      photocopy of typed script. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Crest" (Box 6, Folder 407-416, Item 411)
    - "Tareyton" (Box 6, Folder 407-416, Item 412)
      Photocopy of typed script. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Music lead sheets Gammons show Bob McCully & Joe Negri
    - "Lisa" (Box 6, Folder 417-419, Item 417)
      photostat of holograph manuscript with typed lyrics attached. Two copies.
    - "I Like the Girls" (Box 6, Folder 417-419, Item 419)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript.
    - "But You Know How People Talk" (Box 6, Folder 420)
      photocopy of typed script and score. 11 pages.
    - "Suburbia" (Box 6, Folder 421-428, Item 421)
      Typed lyrics. Two pages.
    - "Susie cont." (Box 6, Folder 421-428, Item 422)
      typed script and lyrics. 3 pages.
    - "I Feel Great" (Box 6, Folder 421-428, Item 423)
      photocopy of typed lyrics. 1 page.
    - "Class, Come to Order!" (Box 6, Folder 421-428, Item 424)
      photocopy of typed script with handwritten notes.
    - "Knock-Knock" (Box 6, Folder 421-428, Item 425)
      typed script with handwritten notation.
    - "Just One of Those Things" (Box 6, Folder 421-428, Item 426)
      photocopy of typed script with handwritten notations.
    - "Something to Think About" (Box 6, Folder 421-428, Item 427)
      photocopy of typed lyrics marked "final version."
    - "The Machines Are Taking Over" (Box 6, Folder 421-428, Item 428)
      photocopy of typed lyrics with handwritten notations.
    - "Night and the City" (Box 6, Folder 429-436, Item 429)
      photocopy of typed script. 2 pages.
    - "Desdamona Fink" (Box 6, Folder 429-436, Item 430)
      photocopy of typed lyrics with handwritten notation.
    - "The South Hills Village Maid" (Box 6, Folder 429-436, Item 431)
      photocopy of typed script with handwritten notations. 3 pages.
    - "Bachelor's Lament" (Box 6, Folder 429-436, Item 433)
      photocopy of typed lyrics.
    - "The Old Casino" (Box 6, Folder 429-436, Item 434)
      Typed lyrics. 2 pages.
    - "Pittsburgh's Not a Provincial Town" (Box 6, Folder 429-436, Item 435)
      photocopy of typed script.
    - "Pittsburgh is Pretty" (Box 6, Folder 429-436, Item 436)
      photocopy of typed lyrics and script. 3 pages.
    - "Office Girls" (Box 6, Folder 437-441, Item 437)
    - "Dulcinea" (Box 6, Folder 437-441, Item 438)
      holograph manuscript. Two pages.
    - "I.B.M. Girl" Bass (Box 6, Folder 437-441, Item 439)
    - "Meter maids" Bass & Drums (Box 6, Folder 437-441, Item 440)
    - "Where Would You Like to Eat" Rhythm (Box 6, Folder 437-441, Item 441)
      Holograph manuscript 4 pages.
    - "Where Would You Like to Eat" Lead Sheet (Box 6, Folder 437-441, Item 441.1)
      Holograph manuscripts. 5 pages.
    - "We Were First" (Box 7, Folder 443-448, Item 443)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript.
    - "I.B.M. Girl" Guitar (Box 7, Folder 443-448, Item 444)
    - "Love Is" (Box 7, Folder 443-448, Item 445)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript
    - "The World is Going Bananas" (Box 7, Folder 443-448, Item 446)
    - "If We Only Had Gas" (Box 7, Folder 443-448, Item 447)
      photocopy of handwritten lyrics on Robert McCully stationary.
    - "My Hero" (Box 7, Folder 443-448, Item 448)
    - "Pills, Potions, and Sweet Smelling Lotions" (Box 7, Folder 449-455, Item 449)
    - "Pills, Potions, Lotion" (Box 7, Folder 449-455, Item 449.1)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript
    - "Trouble" (Box 7, Folder 449-455, Item 450)
    - "Ecumenical Trio Show -- Ben Gross" (Box 7, Folder 449-455, Item 451)
      Typed listing of show order.
    - "In the Audience Tonight" (Box 7, Folder 449-455, Item 452)
      photocopy of two pages of side by side of holograph manuscript.
    - "The Good Old Days of radio" (Box 7, Folder 449-455, Item 453)
    - "And Evening with Zsa Zsa Gabor" (Box 7, Folder 449-455, Item 454)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript with handwritten notations.
    - "Pgh is a Festival City" (Box 7, Folder 449-455, Item 455)
    - "Who's in Charge of this Ratrace" (Box 7, Folder 456-461, Item 456)
    - "Welcome - Opening" (Box 7, Folder 456-461, Item 457)
    - "Pgh's Not a Provincial town" (Box 7, Folder 456-461, Item 458)
    - "People Are No Damn Good" (Box 7, Folder 456-461, Item 459)
    - "America, The Beautiful" (Box 7, Folder 456-461, Item 460)
      photocopy of typed lyrics
    - "America, the Beautiful Version #2" (Box 7, Folder 456-461, Item 461)
      Photocopy of typed lyrics.
    - Untitled note from Bob McCully to Joe Negri (Box 7, Folder 456-461, Item 461A)
      Typed note from Bob to Joe on pink paper.
    - "Love Is" (Box 7, Folder 462-464, Item 462)
      typed lyrics on onion skin.
    - "Love Is (2)" (Box 7, Folder 462-464, Item 462)
    - "The Wonderful World of Crime" (Box 7, Folder 462-464, Item 463)
      Typed lyrics on onion skin. 3 pages.
    - "The Wonderful World of Crime" (Box 7, Folder 462-464, Item 464)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript with penciled notations. 4 pages.
    - "Conformity" (Box 7, Folder 465-470, Item 465)
      photocopy of typed lyrics with penciled notations.
    - "Conformity" (Box 7, Folder 465-470, Item 466)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. 2 pages.
    - "Lets Sing a Pgh. Song" (Box 7, Folder 465-470, Item 467)
    - "Pgh is Pretty - Opening" (Box 7, Folder 465-470, Item 468)
    - "Night & the City" (Box 7, Folder 465-470, Item 469)
    - "Pgh is a Beautiful Town" (Box 7, Folder 465-470, Item 470)
      holograph manuscript. 6 paes.
    - "Pity the Suburban Housewife" (Box 7, Folder 471-477, Item 471)
      holograph manuscript 3 pages.
    - "Gun registration" (Box 7, Folder 471-477, Item 472)
    - "The 12 Days of Xmas" (Box 7, Folder 471-477, Item 473)
    - "Home Sweet Home" (Box 7, Folder 471-477, Item 474)
      photocopy of typed script with handwritten title.
    - "Harry the Vampire" (Box 7, Folder 471-477, Item 475)
    - "Why Mothers Get Gray" (Box 7, Folder 471-477, Item 476)
      holograph title page only.
    - "Opening Number" (Box 7, Folder 471-477, Item 477)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. 3 pages.
    - "Paper Mache" (Box 7, Folder 478-481, Item 478)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 2 pages.
    - "Confession" (Box 7, Folder 478-481, Item 479)
    - "Good Morning" (Box 7, Folder 478-481, Item 481)
    - "Closing" (Box 7, Folder 482-489, Item 482)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. 1 page.
    - "Welcome" (Box 7, Folder 482-489, Item 483)
    - "Youth of America" (Box 7, Folder 482-489, Item 484)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notations. 3 pages.
    - "Hello, Dolly" (Box 7, Folder 482-489, Item 485)
    - "The Beautiful People of Pittsburgh" vocal lead (Box 7, Folder 482-489, Item 486)
    - "Opening" (Box 7, Folder 482-489, Item 487)
    - "Just Gotta Do It" (Box 7, Folder 482-489, Item 488)
      mimeographed lyrics.
    - "Mame" (Box 7, Folder 482-489, Item 489)
      Typed lyrics. Two pages, stapled.
    - "Desdamona meets Son of Stage Struck", July, 1864 (Box 7, Folder 490)
      holograph manuscript, 3 pages. 2 photocopies.
    - "Intro", May 17, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 491)
      untitled other than "Intro." photocopy of holograph manuscript. 1 page.
    - "Rev. Roly Poly" (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 492)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript, two pages side by side on one page.
    - "The Rev. Holy Roly Poly" (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 493)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript, 2 pages side by side. 4 pages.
    - "Rev. Holy Poly" piano/bass (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 494)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript with computer printed title. pages printed side by side. 6 total.
    - "In the Audience" piano/bass (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 495)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. two pages side by side. 4 pages total.
    - "Ralph Nader" (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 496)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript, 2 pages printed side by side. 4 pages.
    - "Waiting for the Sky bus" (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 497)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. Two pages printed side by side. 2 pages.
    - "Those Wonderful Years" (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 499)
    - "In the Audience Tonight" (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 500)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. Two pages printed side by side.
    - "The Rev. Holy Roly Poly" (Box 7, Folder 491-501, Item 501)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. Two pages printed side by side. 4 pages total.
    - "Staisey Foerster & Hunt" (Box 7, Folder 502-506, Item 502)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. Two pages printed side by side. 3 pages total.
    - "Where Would You Like to Eat?" (Box 7, Folder 502-506, Item 503)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. Two pages printed side by side. 12 pages total.
    - "You Forgot Something, Eve", May 17, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 502-506, Item 504)
      Holograph manuscript. Two pages.
    - "America the Beautiful", 1974 (Box 7, Folder 502-506, Item 505)
      Holograph manuscript. two pages. Arranged by Joe Negri.
    - "America, the Beautiful" (Box 7, Folder 502-506, Item 505.1)
      Typed lyrics. Original and one photocopy.
    - "America, the Beautiful Version #2" (Box 7, Folder 502-506, Item 505.2)
    - "Misty Valley" (Box 7, Folder 502-506, Item 506)
    - "Happy Time" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 507)
    - "Yesterdays" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 508)
    - "Cabaret" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 509)
    - "Spiro" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 510)
    - "Toyland Revisited" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 511)
    - "Opening Number" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 512)
    - "Youth of America" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 513)
    - "Youth of America" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 513.1)
    - "Opening Song Medley" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 514)
      holograph manuscript
    - "The Nude Look" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 515)
    - "Lawrence (?) is a Grand" (Box 7, Folder 507-517, Item 517)
    - "It's Hell to be the age you are" (Box 7, Folder 518-525, Item 519)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. 1 pages.
    - "Toyland Revisited" (Box 7, Folder 518-525, Item 520)
      holograph manuscript. 5 pages.
    - "Sex Education", March, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 518-525, Item 522)
    - "Where did the Time Go?", April 13, 196[4?] (Box 7, Folder 518-525, Item 523)
    - "The Ways of Love" (Box 7, Folder 518-525, Item 524)
    - "Where did the Time Go?", April 13, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 518-525, Item 525)
    - "It's Hell to be the Age You Are" (Box 7, Folder 518-525, Item 518)
      Photocopy of typed lyrics. 3 pages. Stapled.
    - "Hum Whistle & Sing" (Box 7, Folder 526-533, Item 526)
    - "McCully & Negri: Medley" (Box 7, Folder 526-533, Item 527)
    - "Beyond Believing" (Box 7, Folder 526-533, Item 528)
    - "Beyond Believing" (Box 7, Folder 526-533, Item 529)
    - "Spiro" (Box 7, Folder 526-533, Item 530)
    - "Toyland Revisited" (Box 7, Folder 526-533, Item 531)
    - "The Govenor [sic] is a 5 letter word" (Box 7, Folder 526-533, Item 532)
    - "Confidence" (Box 7, Folder 526-533, Item 533)
    - "Spiro", April, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 534-543, Item 534)
      holograph manuscript. 3 pages.
    - "Spiro" (Box 8, Folder 534-543, Item 535)
    - "Playmate of the Month", April 2, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 534-543, Item 537)
    - "Opener" (Box 8, Folder 534-543, Item 538)
    - "Fat Men" (Box 8, Folder 534-543, Item 539)
    - "Civilized Human Beings" (Box 8, Folder 534-543, Item 540)
      Photocopy of typed sketch. 3 page.
    - "Who's Got the Habit?" (Box 8, Folder 534-543, Item 541)
      Lyrics and sketch typed on onion skin. 3 pages.
    - "Dirty Books" (Box 8, Folder 534-543, Item 542)
      Photocopy of typed sketch. 3 pages.
    - "Homecoming" (Box 8, Folder 534-543, Item 543)
      Photocopy of typed script. 5 pages.
    - "Pgh. Not a Provincial Town" (Box 8, Folder 544-550, Item 544)
    - "The Always Hungry Blues" (Box 8, Folder 544-550, Item 545)
    - "Who's in Charge of This Ratrace?" (Box 8, Folder 544-550, Item 546)
    - "Rat Race" (Box 8, Folder 544-550, Item 546.1)
    - "Truly Beautiful" (Box 8, Folder 544-550, Item 547)
    - "One Damn Thing Opener" (Box 8, Folder 544-550, Item 548)
    - "When" (Box 8, Folder 544-550, Item 548A)
      Holograph manuscript. 4 pages. Interior pages marked "Touched Me" and "Woman of Stone."
    - "Our Love is Different" (Box 8, Folder 544-550, Item 549)
      holograph manuscript. interior pages marked "Porto Bay" and "Wait for Me."
    - "Found My Love" (Box 8, Folder 544-550, Item 550)
      holograph manuscript. Verso side labeled "You Touched It."
    - "Crazy Crew Cut" (Box 8, Folder 551-556, Item 551)
      Holograph manuscript. Verso side labeled "Woman of Stone."
    - "Wonder If" (Box 8, Folder 551-556, Item 552)
      Holograph manuscript. Interior pages labeled "Porto Bay" and "You Touched Me"
    - "Wonder If" (Box 8, Folder 551-556, Item 553)
      Holograph Manuscript. Other pages labeled "I Like the Girls" and "Why Can't I Fall in Love."
    - "Great Feelin'" (Box 8, Folder 551-556, Item 554)
      Holograph manuscript. Other pages labeled "I wanted you" and "Tormented."
    - "The White House Shuffle" (Box 8, Folder 551-556, Item 555)
      Photostat of holograph manuscript.
    - "Snow White" (Box 8, Folder 551-556, Item 556)
    - "Snow White" (Box 8, Folder 557-559, Item 557)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 6 pages.
    - "Tormented" (Box 8, Folder 557-559, Item 558)
      Photostat of holograph manuscript. 2 pages.
    - "Tormented" (Box 8, Folder 557-559, Item 558.1)
      Holograph manuscript. 2 page folio.
    - "Crazy Crew Cut Sort of Guy" (Box 8, Folder 557-559, Item 559)
      Photostat of holograph manuscript. typed lyrics stapled to outside.
    - "Wednesday's Child" (Box 8, Folder 560)
      photostat or proof of holograph manuscript with editorial notations.
    - "The Old Days of Radio" (Box 8, Folder 561-564A, Item 561)
      Photocopy of typed lyrics. 3 pages.
    - "The Classroom" (Box 8, Folder 561-564A, Item 563)
      Typed script on onion skin. Two pages, stapled.
    - "Who Will Finish the Season" (Box 8, Folder 561-564A, Item 564)
      Typed script on onion skin with handwritten notes.
    - "The Alcoa Alumaband", November 14, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 561-564A, Item 564A)
      Typed script. 4 pages.
    - "Lisa" (Box 8, Folder 565-571B)
      Photostat of holograph manuscript. two page folio.
    - "Silent Movies" (Box 8, Folder 565-571B, Item 566)
    - "The White House Shuffle" (Box 8, Folder 565-571B, Item 567)
    - "I'm the Girl Who Stole the Key" (Box 8, Folder 565-571B, Item 568)
    - "The Machines are Taking Over" (Box 8, Folder 565-571B, Item 569)
      Holograph manuscript. Two page folio.
    - "Who's in Charge" (Box 8, Folder 565-571B, Item 570)
      holograph manuscript. 1 page. Marked rough draft.
    - "Confidence" (Box 8, Folder 565-571B, Item 571)
      holograph manuscript. Two page folio. Marked "Work Draft."
    - "Machines are taking over" (Box 8, Folder 565-571B, Item 569)
      holograph manuscript. 2 page folio. Verso labeled "They Hate US."
    - "Pretty Girl" (Box 8, Folder 565-571B, Item 571B)
      Holograph manuscript. Marked "Work Sheet."
    - [Untitled, first line "We're beautiful oo-oo we're ravising"] (Box 8, Folder 572-579, Item 572)
    - "Pills, Potions, and Sweet-Smelling Lotions" (Box 8, Folder 572-579, Item 573)
      typed lyrics on onion skin with handwritten notes. 2 pages.
    - "Give Love a Chance" (Box 8, Folder 572-579, Item 574)
    - "Apple Tree" (Box 8, Folder 572-579, Item 575)
    - "Just One of Those Things" (Box 8, Folder 572-579, Item 576)
    - "Character study" (Box 8, Folder 572-579, Item 577)
      typed sketch. One copy.
    - "Campaign Talk" (Box 8, Folder 572-579, Item 578)
      typed script. 1 page.
    - "You Touched Me" (Box 8, Folder 572-579, Item 579)
    - "Stewardess" (Box 8, Folder 580-586, Item 580)
    - "Conformity" (Box 8, Folder 580-586, Item 581)
    - "I Enjoy Being a Girl" (Box 8, Folder 580-586, Item 582)
    - "They Hate Us", May 2, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 580-586, Item 583)
    - "Woman of Stone" (Box 8, Folder 580-586, Item 584)
    - "Give Love a Chance" (Box 8, Folder 580-586, Item 586)